<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SPatch</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="sp_app">Apps</string>
    <string name="sp_mod">Modules</string>
    <string name="sp_sk_info">SK Team Not only infomation masterly but master all.</string>
    <string name="visit_sk">Visit</string>
    <string name="sp_ensure_local_ext">Which place you wanna select from? You can select external apk from file explorer.</string>
    <string name="sp_install_from_local">Local</string>
    <string name="sp_install_from_ext">External</string>
    <string name="sp_processing_apk">Processing...</string>
    <string name="sp_mod_success">Modify Success</string>
    <string name="sp_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="sp_app_loc">Your new application package may locate at</string>
    <string name="sp_install">Install It</string>
    <string name="sp_now_install">Do you wanna install immediately? Note: You must uninstall origin application before you install this application.</string>
    <string name="sp_deny">Deny</string>
    <string name="sp_failed_help">This application may not be supported. Please try again or change versions of application.</string>
    <string name="sp_mod_failed">Modify Failed</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select_app">Select Application</string>
    <string name="sp_select">Select</string>
    <string name="sp_back">Back</string>
    <string name="sp_loading">Loading data...</string>
    <string name="sp_load_complete">Load Finish.</string>
    <string name="sp_game_tips">Pull down and let go for gaming, hold up for game continuing.</string>
    <string name="sp_mod_add2list">Use Module</string>
    <string name="sp_mod_rem_from_list">Do Not Use</string>
    <string name="sp_ensure_add_mods">Do you wanna add those mod(s)?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SK Settings</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_non_modify">Non APK Modify Mode</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_alert_when_done">Show Notification When Task Done</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_unpack">Auto  Unpacking</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_disable_mod">Disable All Modules</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_disable_safe_mode">Disable Safe Mode Temporarily</string>
    <string name="sp_settings_test_mode">Debug Mode</string>
    <string name="sp_core_load_failed">SPatch core load failed. Please examine libs and ensure all need files were in right place. (Are you change your settings recently?)</string>
    <string name="sp_core_load_failed_title">SK Fatal Error</string>
    <string name="sp_core">SPatch Core</string>
    <string name="sp_core_dsp">SPatch core. A powerful and Fuocoso heart!</string>
    <string name="sp_info">SPatch is a software that enables native applications to load Xposed modules without ROOT or unlock. There are three operation modes of Tianjian: modified APK mode, modified-free mode and global mode. Simply click on the application + number and select the application installation package according to the prompt to use the module easily. It supports a variety of modules, including the Xposed module you made yourself. It also supports the integration of modules into the installation package (in the module list, click on the module information and use the module). At present, it can enable or close the global mode and no modification mode in the settings page. The application needs to be rebuilt after opening the modifier-free mode. It can be set up to send information to the notification bar after each application is built. It can also be set up to disable the whole module, intelligent shelling and anti-reinforcement functions (intelligent shelling, anti-reinforcement and non-modification construction applications need to download additional native library files). In addition, it can open debugging mode and disable security mode in the settings. To facilitate developers to analyze the work of the module. The reconstructed application will load all modules installed locally by default, and the integrated module will no longer rely on the module software installed locally, so that the installation package can be shared with others. Note that the modifier-free mode relies on the application of the almanac. If the application of the almanac is uninstalled, all application data of the modifier-free mode will be empty and unrecoverable. The global mode also relies on the application of the heavenly observer. When the global mode is enabled, if the application of the heavenly observer is uninstalled, all the modules of the heavenly observer will be invalid. This application is only for learning. Because the application has the function of anonymous information collection, it will require the information rights of mobile phones. The information collected by this application may contain your privacy information. We will not share your information with third parties without your authorization. This information is only for our analysis and use. Please make sure that users with confidentiality requirements will not collect your confidential information, and we will not be responsible for your information leakage. This application may damage your equipment, we will not be responsible for changes in your equipment, if your equipment after using this application crash, can not boot, overheating and so on, please report to us. Author: Haili (QQ 384550791), website http://www.fou.ink/, the right of final interpretation of this application belongs to the author. If you continue to use this software, you will receive all the agreements. Thank you for your understanding and support. Thank you very much for GanYao (SandHook author, who provides strong support for the core technology of this application), Windy (Xpatch author, who provides ideas for application implementation), Lody (Whale framework developer), JCoder (thank the big guy for helping to implement the reinforcement and restoration technology), Liu Hengfu (who provides ideas for application core), and Ningru.（ Thank you for fixing several serious BUGs in the no-modification mode, as well as my application users and testers. Thank you for supporting this application!</string>
    <string name="sp_about">About SPatch</string>
    <string name="sp_search">Search Apps...</string>
    <string name="app_powered_by">Powered by SandHook</string>
    <string name="sp_supersu">SU</string>
    <string name="sp_require_su">%s is applying for super user permission, accept? Notice: some application may do harm for your personal computer with root access. If you have less knowledge of this application, press deny for sound.</string>
    <string name="sp_launch">Launch</string>
    <string name="sp_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="sp_launch_app_now">Do you wanna launch application immediately?</string>
    <string name="sp_install_success">Installation success. Pull down list for refresh, you can launch application by click application list.</string>
    <string name="sp_open_mod_settings">Module Settings</string>
    <string name="sp_nonmod_enable_tips">Congratulations! You now unlock non-modify mode, this mode can run application in non-modify and need no resign apk. You can only select application local, and you can click use module in alert dialog as you click module in modules list.</string>
    <string name="sp_unpack_enable_tips">Congratulations on unlocking the shelling function. Please re-add the application. The files from the application dump will be stored in the application external storage data directory.</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor">APK Editor</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_dexedit">Edit Dex File</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_class">Class</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_arsc">Arsc Translate</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_xml">XML Editor</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_crack_sign">Signing Crack</string>
    <string name="sp_hexeditor">HEX Editor</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_translate">Translate Resource</string>
    <string name="sp_apkeditor_method">Method</string>
    <string name="sp_perm_setting">Permission Setting</string>
    <string name="sp_new_modify_mode">V2 Modify Mode</string>
    <string name="sp_create_shortcut">Create Shortcut</string>
    <string name="sp_app_settings">App Settings</string>
    <string name="sk_modifyv2_patch">Select Patch File</string>
    <string name="sp_perm_must_allow">Permission Storage And Phone Stats is required. Please enable those permission in System Settings - App Settings - Permission.</string>
    <string name="sp_user_privacy_policy">User Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="sp_user_privacy_policy_detail">This application respects and protects the privacy of all users who use the service. In order to provide you with more accurate and personalized services, this application will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy. However, this application will treat this information with a high degree of diligence and prudence. Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, the application will not disclose or provide such information to third parties without your prior permission. This application will update this privacy policy from time to time. When you agree to this application service usage agreement, you are deemed to have agreed to the full content of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of this application service usage agreement. This Agreement applies to users of all ages. Please accept the privacy agreement under the age of 14 under the escort of guardians. 1. Scope of application (a) When you use the application network service or visit the web page of the application platform, the application automatically receives and records the non-privacy information on your browser and computer, including your IP address, the type of browser, the language used, the date and time of access, the software and hardware characteristics information and the web page record data you need; You understand and agree that the following information does not apply to this privacy policy: (a) The information collected by the application about your use of the application, including but not limited to application-in-application virtualization application information, application virtualization application installation information, permissions required for In-Application services, application crash and unique identifiers of users; (b) Violation of the law or the rules of application and the measures taken by the application to you (c) the application itself will not take the initiative to collect your privacy information, but it may collect your privacy information as follows: if you have installed QQ and QQ software, you may call QQ and indirectly access your privacy information. If you collect the information, you will take the privacy agreement of the two parties as the criterion. Gender information, property information, communication records and contents, credit information, trajectory, accommodation information, health and physiology information, transaction information and personal information of minors under 14 years old. (d) The application may call an external application, which may provide some privacy or non-privacy information to you, whichever is the privacy protocol of the external application. 2. Information Use (a) The application will not provide, sell, rent, share or trade your personal information to any unrelated third party unless prior permission is obtained from you, or the third party and the application (including the affiliated company of the application) provide services to you individually or jointly, and after the end of the service, they will be prohibited from accessing all such information, including all that they have previously been able to access. (b) This application also does not allow any third party to collect, edit, sell or disseminate your personal information free of charge by any means. If any user of this application platform engages in the above activities, the application has the right to terminate the service agreement with that user immediately upon discovery. (c) The information collected by this application will be used for advertisement pushing, user cheating analysis and disclosure of cheating, registration of accounts and enjoyment of our community services, application experience improvement, entity and virtual goods transactions, information security trend analysis. 3. Information Disclosure Under the following circumstances, this application will disclose your personal information in whole or in part according to your personal wishes or legal provisions: (a) Disclosure to third parties with your prior consent; (b) To provide the products and services you require, you must share your personal information with third parties; (c) Disclosure to third parties or administrative or judicial bodies in accordance with the relevant provisions of the law or the requirements of administrative or judicial bodies; (d) if you appear in violation of Chinese laws, regulations or the application service agreement or the relevant rules, you need to disclose it to the third party. (e) If you are a qualified intellectual property complaint and have lodged a complaint, you should disclose it to the respondent at the request of the respondent so that both parties can handle possible rights disputes; (f) In a transaction created on this application platform, if either party has fulfilled or partially fulfilled its transaction obligations and made a request for information disclosure, the application has the right to decide to provide the user with necessary information such as the contact mode of the other party of the transaction, so as to facilitate the completion of the transaction or the settlement of disputes. (g) Other disclosures that the application deems appropriate in accordance with laws, regulations or application policies. 4. Information Storage and Exchange (a) The information and information collected by this application about you will be stored on the server of this application and/or its affiliated company. This information and information may be transmitted to your country, region or overseas where the information and information collected by this application are located and accessed, stored and displayed abroad. (b) Any information about you can be retained during your use. You do not use this application and write off your account as not using it. The information you never use will be retained for no more than 180 days. You can contact us to delete, change or obtain the information we have collected about you. 5. Use of Cookies (a) If you do not refuse to accept cookies, the application will set or access cookies on your computer so that you can log in or use cookies-dependent application platform services or functions. This application uses cookies to provide you with more thoughtful personalized services, including promotional services. (b) You have the right to accept or reject cookies. You can reject cookies by modifying browser settings. But if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to log in or use cookies-dependent native application network services or functions. (c) The relevant information obtained through cookies set up in this application will be applicable to this policy. 6. Information Security (a) This application account has security protection function. Please keep your username and password information properly. This application will ensure that your information is not lost, abused and altered by encrypting user passwords and other security measures. Despite the aforementioned security measures, please also note that there is no \"perfect security measures\" on the information network. (b) When using this application network service for online trading, you will inevitably have to deal with the counterparty or potential trading pair. 7. Changes in the Privacy Policy (a) if we decide to change the privacy policy, we will publish these changes in this policy, our website and where we think it is appropriate so that you can understand how we collect, use your personal information, who can access this information, and under what circumstances we will disclose this information. (b) The Company reserves the right to amend this policy at any time, so please check it frequently. If any major changes are made to this policy, we will inform you by way of website notification. 8. User\'s Rights and Duties (a) Please protect your personal information properly and provide it to others only when necessary. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially the username and password (or unique identifier) of this application has been leaked, please contact the application customer service immediately so that the application can take appropriate measures. (b) the main body of operation is contact: Company Name: Xin Wei Information Security Co., Ltd., registered address: No. 18 industrial road, Shuangliu District, Zhejiang Province. Contact: Miss Fang. E-mail: king@die.lu, QQ: 384550791.</string>
    <string name="sp_wait_for_engine">Starting Engine...</string>
    <string name="sp_unknown_error">Unknown Error</string>
    <string name="sp_engine_startup_success">Engine startup success!</string>
    <string name="sp_kill_engine">VSK Engine is now exiting, leaving single: 0.</string>
    <string name="backup_restore">Backup And Restore</string>
    <string name="sp_backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="sp_restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="sp_backup_restore_tips">You can backup all inner application data by click backup button. Your backup file will save at %s, and you can also restore all your application data by click restore button. You must restart this application while restore finish.</string>
</resources>
